freecampsites.net 2019-02-07

# Privacy Policy - Freecampsites.net

This Privacy Policy has been created so that you, as a user of this website, understand how the data that you submit to us is handled.

**Your Email Address**  
We do not use your email address for anything other than:  
* To confirm that you are an actual person during the registration process.  
* To respond to a query or comment that you have submitted to us.  
* To inform you of a comment on one of the campsites that you have submitted.  
Your email address is NEVER seen by a third party. You will receive emails when someone comments on a campsite that you have submitted. This is an automated process and the commenter does not have access to your email address.  
At this time, we do not send out mailings to our users. If we ever do, you will have the ability to opt out.

**Cookies**  
Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small text files – “cookies” – that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account. We use cookies to save your preferences and login information, and provide personalized functionality. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but be aware that this will disable some of the functionality on the website. More information about cookies can be found at <https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie>.

**Your Account**  
You are free to change your account information at any time. If desired, you can also close your account with us at anytime. Once the account is closed, all identifying information that you entered into your profile will be removed from our servers. Your submitted locations, reviews, and content will remain but will be placed under an administrator’s account.

**Third Parties**  
We do not provide any personally identifying information that you have submitted to us to any third parties for any reason other than to comply the law. We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. 

Please be aware that any information that you include on the “Submit A Campsite” form, including images and documents that you upload, will be publicly visible once submitted. Comments are also visible to everyone. However, the email address that you place in the “Email” field on the comment submission form is visible only to the administrators of FreeCampsites.net

We utilized trending services provided by Google. Please see the [Google Analytics Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html) for more information.

**Ads**  
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by FreeCampsites.net and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Our Store**  
Our online store is powered by Amazon.com. Any information exchanges are covered in [their Privacy Policy](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496)

**Business Transfers**  
If FreeCampsites.net, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that FreeCampsites.net goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of FreeCampsites.net may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our site and servers, track access, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. It is possible that personal information about a customer may be included in the log files due to the normal functions of IP addresses and Web browsing.

**Data Protection**  
We are protected by an extensive custom firewall rule and large mod_security rulesets protecting our servers. Our servers are located in highly secure facilities with restricted access.

Our other security methods and precautions are confidential.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please email us at admin@freecampsites,net. You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details from any list under our control.

**Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy.**

**Change Log**  
2011/14/07 – created
